module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'The chicken genome was sequenced in what year making it the first bird sequenced.',
      a: '2002',
      b: '2005',
      c: '2008',
      d: '1999',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which bird family gave us the domesticated chicken?',
      a: 'Pheasants',
      b: 'Grouse',
      c: 'Warblers',
      d: 'Thrushes',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'An elephant never forgets anything! What do chickens never forget?',
      a: 'A smell',
      b: 'A sound',
      c: 'A face',
      d: 'Another chicken',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'How many eyelids to chickens have?',
      a: '4',
      b: '3',
      c: '2',
      d: '1.5',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Humans are up to 60% water. What percent water is a chicken?',
      a: '40%',
      b: '50%',
      c: '61',
      d: '75',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'Run, Chicken, Run! How fast can poultry pound the pavement?',
      a: '3 mph',
      b: '9 mph',
      c: '11mph',
      d: 'Chickens only fly',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the following is a part of a rooster mating dance?',
      a: 'The Cock-a-doodle-doo',
      b: 'A backflip',
      c: 'A moonwalk',
      d: 'A wing drag',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'We all know a chicken can live with its head cut off. Ew. How long did the longest make it?',
      a: '18 minutes',
      b: '18 days',
      c: '18 weeks',
      d: '18 months',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'What mineral do chickens actively avoid eating?',
      a: 'sodium',
      b: 'potassium',
      c: 'iodine',
      d: 'calcium',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'How many chickens are there on the planet currently?',
      a: '2 billion',
      b: '10 billion',
      c: '25 billion',
      d: '35 billion',
      answer: 'c'
    }
  ]
};